OpenSPP Registry Tutorial - Learn how to register individuals, create groups, and manage beneficiaries
Navigate to Registry > Search to open the Registry Search Portal
Click "New Individual" to register a new person
Enter the individual details: family name, given name, and other required fields
Click Save to register the individual
Search for the newly created individual to verify registration
Click "New Group" to create a household or organization
Opening the group registration form...
Enter the group name and save
Search for the group to verify it was created
Open the group to add members
Click "Add a line" and search for the individual to add as a member
Save the group with the new member