Receiving Donations in DRIMS
Click DRIMS in the sidebar, then select Donations
View the list of all donations for your warehouses
Look for donations with Announced status and click to open
View donation details including incident, warehouse, donor, and status
Click Mark Received when physical goods arrive at your warehouse
Fill in the received date and actual quantities
Click Confirm to save the received status
The donation status changes to Received
Click Inspect to check the quality and condition of items
Check each item condition, quantity match, and quality
Click Complete Inspection when done checking all items
Click Stock to add inspected items to your warehouse inventory
Review the stock receipt showing items and quantities to add
Click Validate to confirm adding items to inventory
The donation is now Stocked and items are in your inventory
Navigate to Inventory > Stock to verify items were added